<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Election Blog 2024 on Victor Bowker</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/election-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Election Blog 2024 on Victor Bowker</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/election-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/election-blog/post/2024/09/14/blog-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/election-blog/post/2024/09/14/blog-post-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is no surprise, nor a secret, that most Americans vote with their pocketbook in mind.&#xA;According to the Pew Research Center in a poll from September 9th of this year, the &lt;em&gt;greatest&lt;/em&gt; concern among both Trump and Harris supporters is the economy. The next greatest issue, health care, is only ranked at highly concerning to 65% of voters, compared to the 81% when asked about the American economy.[1]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/election-blog/post/2024/09/08/blog-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/election-blog/post/2024/09/08/blog-post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello all! I am so excited to begin on this journey of forecasting the 2024 Presidential Election. Please understand that this will be updated often, and I have no guarantee that this projection will be correct! Thanks for reading - VB&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Past Vote Share - Overall&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the more critical aspects of forecasting is understanding the past. Data can be an incredible tool in understanding past elections, will will allow us to predict the next ones. Below, you will see the two party national vote distribution for the past ~70 years, from 1948 to 2020. You should note that elections are closer now than at most times in our recent history. This can make projections more difficult, as votes are less unanimous!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
